Never forget why you are the church.
I want you to turn your Bibles to Revelation 14 tonight.
Last week, we took a deep look at
the 144,000.
SEAL Jews mentioned in Revelation 7.
We compared the principle of being sealed with
the reality that we are sealed in a similar way, even now as
believers and that seal being through the Holy Spirit.
Upon being born again, God gives to us his Holy
Spirit, his Holy Ghost, who guides and directs us in this earthly life.
It is his seal by which we are marked
and identified as belonging to God.
By the way, I know that I say this a whole lot from this
pulpit talking about the Holy Spirit enjoying with us.
That is one of the greatest miracles that we have
through salvation, is that the 3rd part of God.
We believe in God, the Father, God, the Son, God, the Holy Spirit.
The Holy Spirit of the living God dwells
within the believer to guide us and direct us each and
every day that we live on this earth.
Guys, listen, we should never get tired of that.
Amen?
So to reference back to these 144,000, we can
gather, from the flow of the text, their mission was
obviously to proclaim Jesus saves
during the tribulation.
Now, I will go ahead and tell you, this is not
explicitly stated in any portion of text in Revelation.
The fact that the great multitude of evident saints, however,
It's a multitude that cannot be numbered.
There's many from all tribes, all nations, all
tongues, and there are those that were covered by the blood.
Because that comes right after in Revelation 7,
when he introduces the 144,000, we
can equate that to the result of their ministry
during the great tribulation.
Now, again, we do know, without a doubt, this
great multitude are labeled as the ones who came out of the great tribulation
and have washed their robes and made them white in
the blood of the lamb.
Aren't you glad that even in the darkest of dark times on
this earth, God can still save.
Let's think about that for a second.
God can save whenever, however, and whoever.
And so we think great tribulation, I told you, I believe that
God is going to call his church up out of here, so there has to
be some witnesses.
There has to be some proclaiming saints for this to happen.
And so we see here, that's what the 144,000.
Now, Revelation 14, mentions
the 144,000 again.
So last week we looked at verses one through three.
It says this.
And I looked, and Loah, Lamb stood on the Mount Zion and with
him 144,000, having his father's name written on their foreheads.
And I heard a voice from heaven as the voice of many waters,
and as the voice of a great thunder, and I heard the voice of harpers
harping with their harps, and they sung, as it were, a
new song before the throne, and before the 4 beasts and the elders.
And no man could learn that song, but the 144,000,
which were redeemed from the earth.
I want to give you a little commercial here, okay?
Little extra little tidbit, little golden nugget for you.
By the way, students, you are getting right dropped into a pretty intense study, okay?
So if you have no idea what's going on tonight, that's totally fine, all right?
We got notes for you.
It's all online.
You can keep up with it if you want, so just try to keep up if you can, all right?
But, um, notice here and I just
gotta, because it's been a conversation in my personal life with
certain people that I, that I see as friends, but
notice that it says, I heard the voice of harpers harping with
their harps.
Now, what is a harp?
It's a stringed instrument, amen?
Now, listen, I'm not, I don't, there's
certain denominational differences that I don't think is
a salvation issue.
Does that make sense?
For example, whether or not you use instruments, that's your prerogative.
I can tell you right now.
If you took instruments away from the CMAs, we wouldn't go.
Let me say that again.
My dad would for sure not go.
But if you took instruments away from all your favorite bands,
you wouldn't like them as much, would you?
So what I'm trying to say is this.
We acknowledge the skill and the talent that God
has given certain people.
Why do you think he gave that kind of skill?
It wasn't for the flesh.
It was for him.
And so in other words, we worship.
I believe that we are to worship with all the abilities and all the skills that
we have to just give it right back to him.
That's why, listen, I don't care how many instruments we have up here as long
as the heart posture's correct and we're sending it right back to the Lord.
And so we see here that that, no, I understand
in the gospels in the in the New Testament up to
this point, they're not mentioned, but they're mentioned at the end.
And so obviously God has a plan for instruments.
Okay, go to nugget over.
Amen?
So we see here that there is more description of these Jewish
gospel spreaders.
And this description can get a little odd.
So let's look at verses 4 through 5 here, and let's see what God has to say.
It says this.
These are they which were not defiled with women.
For they are virgins.
We speaking of the 144,000.
These are they which follow the land with us whoever he goeth.
These were redeemed from among men being the 1st fruits unto God and to the lamb.
And their in their mouth was found no God, in other words, no lies.
For they are without fault before the throne of God.
In other words, they are found blameless.
Now, what in the world does this mean?
And I'll be honest with you.
So last week it didn't really match with the flow of the of the
lesson, and I've had multiple questions say, hey, why did you stop at verse three?
Why did you keep on reading?
And so as I went to the study?
I was like, you know what?
God has something for us here.
And so what does this mean?
Does it mean just what it says?
And if so, why?
Does it mean what it says?
So before we get to it, let's pray for some wisdom and discernment.
Probably thank you, Lord, for even a difficult text.
God, I pray that you open our eyes, give us wisdom, give us understanding, the
sermon tonight, to understand exactly, Lord, what
you would have us understand God.
I pray that even in the times that we don't understand that
we don't know all the details, God, I pray that you strengthen our faith in those moments.
God, we don't know exactly when, how, where, but we do know who,
and that's Jesus Christ, and we thank you for him.
So God, I pray, Lord, that you just open our hearts, open our minds, and open our ears.
Since Jesus, I ain't praying.
Everybody said?
Amen.
This is one of the honest and confounding scriptures in Revelation.
I mean, at 1st glance, it seems pretty simple.
The 144,000 were virgin men who were purchased of God, and they were blameless.
So what are the differing views that can be rendered from this text because
if you are going to learn anything about Revelation, there are
many, many differing views about just about everything that's in the book.
And so we're going to 1st look at some of the complexities here.
In the New Testament, the concept of virginity is almost
always used to refer to a woman rather than a man.
So within the Greek term used here.
We can see this truth.
That Greek term Parthenos means
virgin, referring to a female woman, but it also can occasionally
refer to a male man of marriageable age,
focusing on his or her virginity.
As a matter of fact, another little out of the Lexham theological
workbook, a wordbook, rather, it says this, this
term almost always refers to a young woman of marriageable age,
who has never had physical relations with a man.
The only exception is in Revelation 144,
which refers to males.
Jesus' mother is referred to as this term and fulfillment
of Isaiah 714.
We can see that in Matthew chapter one.
Metaphorically speaking, Paul refers to the church as
a holy pure virgin, whom he feels obligated to protect,
according to 2 Corinthians 112.
We'll read that here in just a little bit, imploring the imagery of
a father preserving his daughter's purity for her husband.
So we see here that there's some complexities to this text.
So here lies the dilemma.
Is this a loan exception to the use of the word?
Or is this simply a semantical phenomenon
that reveals a more complex meaning?
To answer this, we have to look at the main 2 interpretations of this text.
And I'm sure that you can guess, if you've learned anything from Revelation,
What are typically the 2 views of
each text that we can go to?
You got the literal view and the symbolic view.
So the 1st interpretation sees this as obviously literal.
It is important to note that whenever it is possible to interpret the
Bible with a literal reading, it is best to do so.
Reading everything in God's word is
symbolic is a good way to become a heretic.
Understand this
If everything is symbolic in
God's word, that means that really everything is just up to
what you see it as symbolizing.
Therefore, you can put your own interpretation,
you can put your own twist on the Bible, and that's what
people have done in our society.
I don't know if you saw it or not and it caused a whole bunch of
ruffled feathers, but I posted, I just get so tired on
Facebook of seeing all these people, trying to justify
away the church and attending church.
I don't understand how you can read the New Testament and
not see the beauty and the necessity of the New
Testament local church.
So I just said, listen, hey, go to church, serving church.
love Jesus, love the same, like I did all these things.
And meant the people, literally, that would, there was just
a few people that would respond.
And it was just like, listen, hey, I see that
scripture, but that's not how when I get out of it.
And what I'm trying to tell them is this.
It doesn't matter how you feel about God's word.
It matters about your obedience to God's word.
Listen, if you think I feel good every time I preach a
text, you're wrong.
As a matter of fact, the past few Sundays, I'm going to be honest with you.
God's been eating my breakfast, lunch, and dinner.
I've been having to make some decisions spiritually
in my mind and my heart posture that were not comfortable for me in my life.
I was having to make some phone calls and reach out to people because I
want to be devoted to them.
What I'm trying to say is this.
If you're only looking for feelings, guess what?
You'll get them, but you won't get truth.
Are you with me?
So we cannot look at everything symbolic, all right?
That's a dangerous hermeneutical strategy.
Now, hermeneutics.
We went over this not too long ago.
This is the method and principle of interpreting the Bible.
And before you say, that's just for preachers and seminary
students, understand that every time you read God's word,
you are using some form of hermeneutics.
Okay?
So you are a Bible scholar, just like I'm a Bible scholar.
Isn't that pretty cool?
Amen?
So if we take this literal, what does it mean?
Not to sound smart, but with a literal reading, it means exactly what it says.
Amen.
These are Jewish men, 12,000 from each tribe.
They have never had physical relations with a woman.
They're completely and utterly committed to the Lord.
They were bound to tell the truth, and they were found blameless.
That is, without defect, morally.
Well, that just seems too good to be true.
How could there be 144,000 men like that?
Well, it really shouldn't surprise us too much because we
see in scripture, Paul gives us a
pretty valid reason to be wholeheartedly committed to the Lord.
As a matter of fact, in 1st Corinthians 7, verse 7 through 8,
he says this, yet I wish that all men were even as myself am.
However, each man has his own gift from God, one in this manner and another in that.
But I say to the unmarried and to the widows, that it is good
for them if they remain even as I.
In other words, he's saying, listen, if you don't have to get married, don't get married.
Give yourself fully to the Lord.
Now, now he explains it later.
First Corinthians 7 in verse 32 says, but
I want you to be free from concern.
One who is unmarried is concerned about the things of the Lord,
how he may please the Lord, but one who is married is concerned about the
things of the world, how he may please his wife.
Some of the men in here say amen.
You understand what we're saying here?
And his interests are divided.
The woman who is unmarried and the virgin is concerned about the things of the Lord,
that she may be holy both in body and spirit.
The one who is married is concerned about the things of the world, how she may please her husband.
Women in here say amen.
Is I say for your own benefit?
Why are the men so much louder in that situation?
That's crazy.
This I say for your own benefit, not to put a restraint upon you, but
to promote what is appropriate and to secure undistracted devotion
to the Lord.
You don't have to be married for long to realize the validity of this truth here.
When you are married, you have other things to worry about.
When you are not married, God can use you, however, he wants whenever he wants.
Now, that doesn't mean you can't be used by God married.
You understand what I'm saying, but we're seeing here the principle
is that there are certain things that you have
to be worried about or concerned about, rather, in
a marriage that's taking care of your family.
They are smack dab, though.
If we look at the 144,000, with this in mind, think about it.
They are smack dab in the most horrific and miserable time the
world has ever seen.
The great tribulation has literally taken place right before their very eyes.
They don't have time to be concerned about family.
They are completely and wholly on gospel mission.
Now it is important to understand that this
text in 1st Corinthians and Revelation 14 is
not putting a negative connotation on marriage.
Again, you can't read your Bible and not realize that marriage, they give from God.
Rather, Revelation 14.
is emphasizing the urgency of this particular time.
Allow me to give you another side note here.
If there is such an obvious difference in these men that they're
purity or their virginity is something that they are known by,
it is logical to assume that during the great tribulational
period people are going to continue to have families.
You say, well, what does that matter?
Well, this should give us an urgency as believers to turn as many families
to Christ as possible right now.
In other words, I don't I don't want anyone to have to go through that.
I don't want any, now it's going to happen, right?
We can't we can't get to everybody, but I was reading an article.
You realize that less than 30% of Americans.
Less than 30.
Now, look, you can say whatever you want about statistics, but here's one that I saw today.
Less than 30% of Americans.
The greatest nation in the world.
the most free nation in the world, the
most religiously free nation in the world, under 30%
of Americans claim that they've ever been shared the gospel with.
In other words, we're just not sharing the gospel.
And so when we talk about the great tribulation, we
talk about what is to come for those who are lost, or
even then, even if we, if the Lord tarries and they die in their
losses and go to hell, guys, this should give us urgency to
proclaim that Jesus saves just like was the
mission for these men.
Another reason to take this text literal is that the concept
of being blameless in such a wicked generation is not
a foreign concept in scripture.
Anyone remember a man named Noah?
Yeah, Noah?
What did Noah build?
He builds an ark, amen?
Why y'all so slow with that?
Listen, so I told y'all last week that I'll be, um,
I'll be the Bible teacher for Olive Branch education, starting
in August, and I'm going to give a quiz,
really an assessment, rather, the 1st class on to
see how much, um, they know about the Bible, just simple things.
And we take that for granted sometimes.
And I want to be careful.
I'm not going to give no names, but there was a young man not, you know, probably years and years ago.
And, you know, he had grew up going to
church here or there and stuff, but we were in life groups one time
and he straight up came to me afterwards and said, man, I learned something tonight.
And I was like, what are you talking about?
He said, I did not realize a David that killed Goliath was the
king David that we always talk about.
And listen, immediately, you know me, I'm like, man, you silly foolish.
Like, what are you talking about, bro?
Like who taught you?
But you know what?
You know what actually happened?
My heart broke.
And what are you talking about?
In other words, we take for granted our freedom
so much that we abuse it and we don't actually, we
don't worry about any of this.
We just kind of go through the motions.
But Noah, I don't know why I did all that to you.
I know you know who Noah is.
He built the ark, okay?
We got some good folks up in here.
Genesis 6 5 says this.
Then the Lord saw that the wickedness of man was great on the earth, and
that every intent of the thoughts of his heart was only evil continually.
So God decided we know to blot out man from the face of the land.
That sounds like everything is over and done with.
He sends, you know, he sends the flood, but that's not really what happened.
Look at Genesis 6, 8, 9 or listen, rather.
But Noah found favor in the eyes of the Lord.
Why?
These are the records of the generation of nowhere.
Noah is a righteous man.
Look at the word, aimless in his time.
Noah walked with God.
If we look at this in the light of Revelation, what did Noah's
blameless character accomplish?
In the midst of the greatest act of judgment up to that point
in the history of the world, the flood that took
out all the people, such terror from God that
he promised never to destroy the earth in such manner again?
Think about that for a second.
Every time we see a rainbow, we need to remember the promise
God gave that he'll never destroy the earth with water again.
That's how bad it was.
The countless lives that were lost.
Yet 8 were saved.
Eight were delivered.
Who would this say?
Noah, his wife, his 3 sons, and their wives.
In other words, because he found favor with God.
Because he was blameless in such a wicked generation,
people were saved from God's wrath.
Are you understanding the similarities here?
Are you seeing a parallel that we see in scripture?
Because of the 144,000, the seal that God puts on
them, their character and decision of all the Lord completely, their
sacrifice to put their calling and mission above all else, what will this accomplish?
Men, women, and children from all over the world will come to know Christ in
the midst of the greatest pouring out of wrath, God will ever do.
This is not a part of revelation that we ought to overlook.
This is a beautiful promise from God that even when it seems like all hope is gone.
There is hope in Jesus.
That is the literal view.
By the way, if God's wrath came right now.
Who would be saved because of your witness and testimony?
Because of your mission, Your commitment
to sharing the gospel.
Who would be delivered from the wrath?
Guys that's a very sobering question for me.
I don't like going too long without leading someone to Christ.
Amen?
And you say, oh, well, I don't understand how you could lead someone to Christ in
such a generation where everyone questions everything and no
one wants to talk and all this stuff.
Listen, hey people want to talk.
And if we go in with the Holy Spirit and we say, God, you know what, show me
the way today, give me opportunity, I guarantee you this, he'll give it to you.
And as long as you plant the seed, maybe you're one that waters the seed.
Hey, guess what?
God could use you to harvest the seed, but either way, we got
to have a, we got to have a part in the sharing and proclamation of
the gospel of Jesus Christ.
If you're with me, say amen.
So that's a literal view.
But there are those who take a symbolic view.
Now we're going to move fast from here, okay?
Remember last week, the 144,000
in some eyes could simply be a symbol of the church as a whole.
Remember, symbolic view.
That is the completed church.
He uses the number, and he just represents the whole church with that.
This line of thinking would take the literal description would get in
chapter 14 and turn it into a moral symbol of
their devotion and sacred sacred state to the Lord.
Since this is the only use of the concept of virginity regarding
a man rather than a woman, John using this language is
simply speaking of their commitment to Christ.
So it's not that the 144,000 are physical men that
are physical virgins, but rather they have kept themselves
from the adultery of idol worship speaking of the church.
In a lot of this view, we do see in scripture that it equates
auto worship with adultery.
I told you, we're going to read 2nd Corinthians 11, chapter 11, verse 2.
He says this, for I'm jealous over you with a godly jealousy,
for I have espoused you to one husband.
Then I may present you as a chaste version to Christ.
In other words, God is a jealous God of us.
He doesn't want our devotions to be divided.
You understand what I'm saying?
Listen, hey, you know, if now I'm not a fighter, amen?
Any of y'all fighters?
I like to fight.
Some of y'all just like to fight.
Ethan, you like to fight, bud?
Okay.
So if he ever gets mad, just don't get near him.
He likes to fight.
But I'm not a fighter, but I can tell you this.
I can tell you that if I saw if I saw some dude trying to
talk to my woman, I'm not, I may not fight,
fight, but I'm on, it's going to look like I'm going to here in a real quick second.
You understand what I'm saying?
Why?
Because I'm jealous over her.
That's she's mine.
Heaven Lanham is mine, right?
She's nobody else's
And so, in other words, we give our life to the Lord.
Guess whose we are?
We're gods.
We are the bride of Christ.
He is jealous over us.
So when we divide our devotions and we divide our worship.
When we divide our commitment.
Listen, hey, he calls that spiritual adultery.
In ancient Israel, to follow Baal was to be guilty
of just that spiritual adultery.
Now, here's the issue with the symbolic reading of Revelation 14.
First off, there are much clearer ways to speak about spiritual purity.
Or at least there's much different ways that isn't
as explicit and isn't as clear and precise
as what we see in Revelation 14.
The language used here is simply too specific.
These are they which were not defiled with women, for they are virgins.
In a current society that we live in, people will do all they can
to believe and explain away the fact that God will use men for certain purposes.
And listen, I'm not trying to get into all that again, but what I'm trying to say is,
it's not that he doesn't use women.
That's seen throughout all the Bible.
You don't have to read the Bible very long to understand that
God uses anybody that he wants to.
However, Here he decides to use men.
Also, if it was simply moral purity, the rest of
the description would have been enough to convey that message.
He wouldn't have had it include the fact they were not defiled
with men and virgins.
Now, why is it then that God chooses to use these particular 144,000 Jewish men?
And really, this is where it kind of comes down to.
And we've got to understand this and trust this.
It's because that it's God's plan and he gets to choose the details.
Amen?
So why, before we move on to this part of Revelation.
I do want to point out 2 important parts from this text,
even though there are some clear descriptions that we are not expected to have or
have to imitate from these men, there are also things
that we should imitate.
Notice the Bible says they are pure.
We are to keep ourselves pure morally, even though we live
in an impure and wicked world.
Colossians 35 says this, therefore, consider the members of
your earthly body as dead to immorality, impurity, passion,
evil desire, and greed, which amounts to idolatry.
See, God desires his people.
That's his sealed saints.
That's you and I, if you're born again, from that which is unclean and evil.
This concept of in the world, but not of the world is
a difficult balance, if not careful.
People love to point out that Jesus hung out with sinners.
And they want to, they want to excuse that.
They want to justify their actions with all their sin buddies.
Well, well, Jesus hung out with the with the sinners
and the publicans and all the things and even got caught out for it.
Well, 1st off, understand where to imitate Jesus, but you better be careful.
You're not Jesus.
So Jesus, Jesus was the
strongest man to ever walk the earth spiritually.
You understand what I'm saying?
And we sit here and say, well, you know what?
If I want to go to the bar, then I can go to the bar.
If I want to do this, then I can do this.
If I'm going to go there, then I can go there.
All that's fun and dandy, but you better be careful because the
longer you sit in filth, the more filthy you're gonna get.
And so we have to abhor evil.
That is to distance ourselves from evil and wickedness.
Again, I'm not saying we take a legalistic view on things.
What I'm saying is we got to be careful.
Students, I know you're here.
I love that you're here.
Think about this.
In your schools, there's a lot of evil.
There's a lot of wickedness.
It's very easy.
It's the easy way to try to conform to that.
Try to just, well, I love Jesus, but you
know, I have to have friends.
I have to be a part of something.
So that's just kind of where I'm at.
understand something.
The sacrifices you make for Christ and your faith, they're never void.
They're never wasted.
That's an investment in your the rest of your life.
It's the same thing for the adults here tonight.
So we see they were pure.
Not only were they pure, we also see they were, there was no life
found in their mouth, when you are full of the Holy Spirit, line becomes much more difficult.
Have you ever been tempted alive, but you couldn't get it out?
Y'all just lie.
Anytime you think of a lot, you're like, nah, man, it just comes on out.
Listen, I don't know about you, but there's been times, okay,
that I have sat there and I've had an opportunity to lie.
And it was almost had the Holy Spirit just grabbed my tongue and said, don't you do it.
Listen, when you're filled with the Holy Spirit, it's
difficult to proclaim anything but the truth.
Even if it's even if it's complicated, even if it's difficult, even if it's hard to say.
But when you're filled with the flesh, men line comes easy.
Well, it's just a little white lies, just this.
I just trying to get ahead.
Hold up.
That's a fleshly worldview outlook.
So we see here that they were full of the Holy Spirit.
So lion becomes much more difficult.
Why is this a point made here?
Well, in the midst of the great tribulation, it would be an easy way out
to lie about their faith in order to protect themselves.
But notice their protection was already given to them by God.
They were sealed.
They were protected.
When you trust God, no matter the circumstance, proclaiming truth becomes much easier.
Listen, people say all the time, well, don't you worry
about hurting people's feelings from the pulpit.
Well, 1st off, let me let me say something about that.
I don't necessarily worry about it, although I don't like hurting people's feelings.
Does that make sense?
That's something that I've outgrown a lot.
Back in the day, man, I'd like to hurt your feelings and maybe fun to do it, right?
As long as the word says it, I'm going to say, I'm going to say it in a mean way.
But listen, as you start loving people and as God begins
to love you more and more as you grow in your walk and faith, you
realize my job is not necessarily to hurt your feelings, but I do have to tell you the truth.
And so if the truth does hurt your feelings, my thing is this, hey,
let me shepherd you, let's walk through that hurt together, right?
Because I guarantee you, the words hurt you.
The words hurt me, and I'm glad it has.
Because me and brother Bill, he's not here tonight, but
Bill Sanders, he came out and said, man, he said, I know what you're
saying, that the word is supposed to
hurt and all the things, and but it's to
get you to a point to where you're right with God.
In other words, when the word of God convicts you, that 2-edged
sword goes in and hurts going in and hurts coming out, what
that does that guides you and directs you closer to Christ and
the end result is what we want.
So we see here that they could not lie.
But they were also seen as blameless.
This means unblemished.
You do realize that we can live on this earth, yet be unblemished
from its wicked influence.
I'm not saying it's easy.
It's not always convenient.
Not everyone's going to appreciate your unwavering faith.
However, if we are going to make it in this wicked generation.
We must keep ourselves unblemished.
And if we live as such, what will be the result?
Well look at the text again.
Revelation 14, 4.
These are they which were not defiled with women, for they are virgins.
These are they which follow the lamb whithersoever he goeth.
These were redeemed from among men.
Now look at this, being the 1st fruits unto God and to the lamb.
Could it be that because God removes the church from the earth, the light is diminished
in such a way the world has never experienced.
But he commissions 144,000 Jewish men who
are completely committed to the gospel ministry.
Therefore, they serve as the 1st fruits of a great harvest.
In other words, because of their devotion to God during the worst time in the history
of creation, many people get saved.
You do realize that we're not the 1st fruits of Cedar Grove Baptist Church.
The 1st fruits were over 200 years ago.
We're a result of the faithfulness, right?
Of the ministry here, of men and women that
said, hey, upon this hill, again, do I agree with
their locational skills?
Absolutely not.
Go find some flat land, bro.
If I could go back in time.
I will go back in time.
I would not even change the way I dress.
I say, listen, I'm from the future.
Understand something.
You're going to do a lot better for us if you do not pick this deal.
But if you do, it's fine.
But go find some either way.
whatever.
But let me ask you tonight.
We may not be in a tribulation, but the devil is destroying all that he can.
Amen.
Sin has ravished this earth.
Creation is longing for its creator.
The birth pains are becoming more and more obvious.
I believe, beyond a shadow of doubt, the time is near.
My question is simple.
Are you committed to the mission
God has given you?
to be wholly devoted to him and proclaim the gospel to all who are here
in all spaces of our lives.
If we believe in the end, like the Bible teaches.
And we need to realize we don't have time to waste.
If we believe what God's word says is going to happen.
And I believe it's going to happen.
I may not know all the details, but I know it's going to happen.
That should give us urgency to not waste time.
Every moment, every opportunity is precious.
So tonight, with Hezbound, I was closed before we get into some prayer time.